TRISHA PATHAK () Featured

Lead frontend seeking roles in Software Development, Project Management, Application Programming, Web Development, Web Designing, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Performance Tuning, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, GIT



Current Designation: Lead frontend Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Current Company: Unihyr technologies Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Gurgaon Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Gurgaon, Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: React.Js, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Angularjs, Bootstrap, Responsive Web Design, Github, GIT, Redux,

Webpack,

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

I am a Front-End Developer with hands on experience in website development using my understanding on UI/UX variations on the same. I'm enthusiastic and with good managing approach in creating and developing a product and look forward to face the challenges and figure out solutions for it

Work Experience

Unihyr technologies as Lead frontend Sep 2019 to Till Date

Influxive Autonetics as FrontEnd Developer. Sep 2018 to Jul 2019

Notation Software Labs as UI/ UX Developer. Jan 2018 to Sep 2018

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from DIT- Dehradun in 2017

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Diploma in computer science

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JavaScript			
Angular 9			
HTML 5			
CSS 3			
SCSS			
LESS			
Reactjs			
Redux			
GIT			
WEBPACK			
GRUNT			
Angular 2			
SASS			
WORDPRESS			
Figma			
PHOTOSHOP			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization